Finding Aid for the Centennial History Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Branscomb, Harvie (Chancellor) (Box 0021, Folder 118)
- Campbell, Ernest (Dean of the Graduate School) (Box 0021, Folder 119)
- Clanton, Glen (Dean and Deputy Provost) (Box 0021, Folder 120)
- Gardner, Edwin (Treasurer) (Box 0021, Folder 121)
- Grisham, Frank (Director of the Joint University Libraries) (Box 0021, Folder 122)
- Hawley, Bruce (Bus Srv. and Purchasing) (Box 0021, Folder 123)
- Heard, Alexander (Box 0021, Folder 124)
- Hobbs, Nicholas (Provost) (Box 0021, Folder 125)
- Kaludis, George (Vice-Chancellor) (Box 0021, Folder 126)
- Lagemann, Robert (Dean of the Graduate School) (Box 0021, Folder 127)
- Murray, Walter (Opportunity Development Officer) (Box 0021, Folder 128)
- Poindexter, John W. (Vice-Chancellor) (Box 0021, Folder 129)
- Purdy, Rob Roy (Vice-Chancellor) (Box 0021, Folder 130)
- Roberts, Erb (Director of Plant Operations) Roberts, Erb (Director of Plant Operations) (Box 0021, Folder 131)
- McGaw, Robert A. (Secretary of the University) (Box 0021, Folder 132)
- Sarratt, Madison (Vice-Chancellor) (Box 0022, Folder 1)
- Stapleton, Clay (Athletic Director) (Box 0022, Folder 2)
- Voegeli, Jacque (Dean of the College of Arts and Science) (Box 0022, Folder 3)
- Wilcoxon, Reba (Associate to the Chancellor) (Box 0022, Folder 4)
- Wilson, Vernon E. (Vice-Chancellor - Medical Affairs) (Box 0022, Folder 5)
- Wood, David (Dean of Admissions) (Box 0022, Folder 6)
- Centennial History Correspondence - Relocating Commodore Vanderbilt's Papers (Box 0022, Folder 7)
- Centennial History Bibliographic. Citation of Government Documents (Box 0022, Folder 8)
- Centennial History Correspondence - Cain, Byron W. re: Phi Kappa Psi (Box 0022, Folder 9)
- Centennial History Correspondence - A-C (Box 0022, Folder 10)
- Centennial History Correspondence - D-I (Box 0022, Folder 11)
- Centennial History Correspondence - J-O (Box 0022, Folder 12)
- Centennial History Correspondence - P-Z (Box 0022, Folder 13)
- Centennial History Correspondence - Carmichael, O. C., Jr. (Box 0022, Folder 14)
- Centennial History Correspondence - Stahlman, James G. (Box 0022, Folder 15)
- Faculty Biography - "A" (Box 0022, Folder 16)
- General Biography - "A" (Box 0022, Folder 17)
- Faculty Biography - "B" (Box 0022, Folder 18)
- General Biography - "B" (Box 0022, Folder 19)
- Barnard, E. E. (Box 0022, Folder 20)
- Bishop, Miss Aileen (Box 0022, Folder 21)
- General Biography - Brooks, Cleanth (Box 0022, Folder 22)
- Faculty Biography - Buchanan, John Lee (Box 0022, Folder 23)
- Faculty Biography - "C" (Box 0022, Folder 24)
- General Biography - "C" (Box 0022, Folder 25)
- Clement, Andrew E. (Box 0022, Folder 26)
- Faculty Biography - Collins, Denny (Vann Material) (Box 0022, Folder 27)
- Faculty Biography - "D" (Box 0022, Folder 28)
- Faculty Biography - "E" (Box 0022, Folder 29)
- Faculty Biography - "F" (Box 0022, Folder 30)
- Faculty Biography (Arts and Science) - Fleming, Denna F. (Box 0022, Folder 31)
- General Biography - "G" (Box 0022, Folder 32)
- Faculty Biography - "G" (Box 0022, Folder 33)
- Garland, Miss Mary (Box 0022, Folder 34)
- Georgescu-Roegen, Nicholas (Box 0022, Folder 35)
- General Biography - "H" (Box 0022, Folder 36)
- Faculty Biography - "H" (Box 0022, Folder 37)
- Faculty Biography - "H" (Box 0022, Folder 38)
- Faculty Biography - "J" (Box 0022, Folder 39)
- Faculty Biography - "K" (Box 0022, Folder 40)
- General Biography - "K" (Box 0022, Folder 41)
- Kuhlman, A. F. (Box 0022, Folder 42)
- General Biography - Lake, Devereux - Letters re: Frank Crawford Vanderbilt, Wm. Malone Baskervill, VU (Box 0022, Folder 43)
- Faculty Biography - "L" (Box 0022, Folder 44)
- General Biography - "L" (Box 0022, Folder 45)
- General Biography - "M" (Box 0022, Folder 46)
- Faculty Biography - "M" (Box 0022, Folder 47)
- Faculty Biography - "Mc" (Box 0022, Folder 48)
- Faculty Biography - "N" (Box 0022, Folder 49)
- Nashville (Box 0022, Folder 50)
- Nashville Christian Advocate (locations of back issues) (Box 0022, Folder 51)
- Faculty Biography - "P" (Box 0022, Folder 52)
- General Biography - Reynolds, Richard Samuel, Memoirs; "We Would Be Building with Stone…" or, "An Engine (Box 0022, Folder 53)
- Centennial History - Rockefeller and Johns Hopkins Archives (Box 0022, Folder 54)
- Faculty Biography - "R" (Box 0022, Folder 55)
- General Biography - "R" (Box 0022, Folder 56)
- Faculty Biography - "S" (Box 0022, Folder 57)
- Tolman, Herbert Cushing (Box 0022, Folder 58)
- Faculty Biography - "T" (Box 0022, Folder 59)
- General Biography - "T" (Box 0022, Folder 60)
- Vanderbilt, Frank Crawford (Box 0022, Folder 61)
- Vann, Elizabeth (Box 0022, Folder 62)
- Wilson, E. E. (Box 0022, Folder 63)
- Faculty Biography - "W" (Box 0022, Folder 64)
- Winton, George R. - (Description of) Letters in Centennial History Office (Box 0022, Folder 65)
- General Biography - Woodrow Wilson (Box 0022, Folder 66)
- Vann, Eugene - Centennial History (Box 0022, Folder 67)
- Commodore Cornelius Vanderbilt and his Descendants (Box 0022, Folder 68)
- General Biography - Vanderbilt Family (Box 0022, Folder 69)
- Changing Status - Nationalism (Box 0022, Folder 70)
- Changing Status - Regionalism - Southern Rural Life Council (Box 0022, Folder 71)
- Changing Status - Town and Gown (Box 0022, Folder 72)
- Changing Status - Town and Gown - Football (Box 0022, Folder 73)
- Changing Status - Town and Gown - Urban Renewal - Eminent Domain (Box 0022, Folder 74)
- Changing Status - Regionalism (Box 0022, Folder 75)
- Changing Status - Town and Gown - Land Use Policy Form (Box 0022, Folder 76)
- Changing Status - Town and Gown - The Real Dirt (Box 0022, Folder 77)
- Changing Status - Town and Gown - Urban Renewal (Box 0022, Folder 78)
- Changing Status - M. E. Church, Vanderbilt University and The Christian Advocate, 1895-1900 (Box 0022, Folder 79)
- Changing Status - M. E. Church - General Conference 1898 (Box 0022, Folder 80)
- Changing Status - M. E. Church 1895-1904 (Box 0022, Folder 81)
- Changing Status - M. E. Church 1905-1909 (Box 0022, Folder 82)
- Changing Status - M. E. Church 1909-1910 Dubose and The Epworth Era (Box 0022, Folder 83)
- Changing Status - M. E. Church - Hustler Oct. 29, Nov. 2, 1910 (Box 0022, Folder 84)
- Changing Status - M. E. Church 1910-15 (Box 0022, Folder 85)
- Changing Status - M. E. Church - Court Record, Dec. 1913 (Box 0022, Folder 86)
- Changing Status - University Center (Box 0022, Folder 87)
- Changing Status - University Center - Carnegie Research Program (Box 0022, Folder 88)
- Changing Status - University Center - Peabody - 1915-1973 (Box 0022, Folder 89)
  Peabody Reflector - March 1935
- Changing Status - University Center - Peabody - 1962-1969 (Box 0022, Folder 90)
- Changing Status - University Center - Peabody - Re: Location (Box 0022, Folder 91)
  Correspondence between James Kirkland H. Kirkland and G. E. B. Officials 12/6/1905 - 4/13/1912
- Changing Status - University Center - Peabody - Affiliation…1914-1927 (Box 0022, Folder 92)
- Changing Status - University Center - Peabody -1875-1970 (Box 0022, Folder 93)
- Changing Status - University Center - Peabody - Branscomb proposals to Calkins (G. E. B.) (Box 0022, Folder 94)
  Re: "Organic Union" 1948
- Changing Status - University Center - Peabody - Buttrick Report 1906-1911 (Box 0022, Folder 95)
- Changing Status - University Center - Peabody - Financial (Box 0022, Folder 96)
- Changing Status - University Center - Peabody - Bruce Payne (Box 0022, Folder 97)
- Changing Status - University Center - Peabody - Kirkland-Gilman Letters 1897-1901 (Box 0022, Folder 98)
- Changing Status - University Center - Peabody - 1904-1915 (Box 0022, Folder 99)
- Changing Status - University Center Other Schools - Scarritt (Box 0022, Folder 100)
- Changing Status - University Center - JUL - 1929-1973 (Box 0022, Folder 101)
- Changing Status - University Center - JUL - Correspondence between J.H. Kirkland, O.C. Carmichael, and GEB Officials, 1935-1939 (Box 0022, Folder 102)
  Correspondence between J. H. Kirkland, O. C. Carmichael and G. E. B. Officials 1935-1939
- Changing Status - University Center - JUL - Dedication Program December 6, 1941 (Box 0022, Folder 103)
- Changing Status - University Center - JUL - Dedication Speeches - The Peabody Reflector Jan. 1942 (Box 0022, Folder 104)
  Peabody Reflector - Jan. 1942
- Changing Status - University Center - JUL - Kuhlman, A. Frederick (Box 0022, Folder 105)
- Changing Status - University Center - JUL - 1929, 1931 (Background) (Box 0022, Folder 106)
- Changing Status - University Center - JUL - Fifth Anniversary (1946) (Box 0022, Folder 107)
- Changing Status - University Center - JUL - 1970-1973 (Box 0022, Folder 108)
- Changing Status - University Center - NUC (including NUCC) (Box 0022, Folder 109)
- Changing Status - University Center - Other Schools - Fisk and Kirkland (Box 0022, Folder 110)
- Changing Status - University Center - Other Schools - Fisk (Box 0022, Folder 111)
- Changing Status - University Center - Other Schools - Meharry (Box 0022, Folder 112)
- Changing Status - University Center - Other Schools - Nashville School of Social Work (Box 0022, Folder 113)
- Changing Status - Discontinued Schools - Dental (Box 0023, Folder 1)
- Changing Status - Discontinued Schools - Pharmacy (Box 0023, Folder 2)
- College General - Administration - Physical Plant (Box 0023, Folder 3)
- College General (Box 0023, Folder 4)
- College General - Academic Freedom (Box 0023, Folder 5)
- College General - Administration - Boards (Box 0023, Folder 6)
- College General - Administration - Faculty Salaries (Box 0023, Folder 7)
- College General - Administration - Finance (Box 0023, Folder 8)
- College General - Education General (Box 0023, Folder 9)
- College General - Education General - Smith, Charles F., "Southern Colleges and Schools" (Box 0023, Folder 10)
- College General - Establishment - 1870-1880 (Box 0023, Folder 11)
- College General - Establishment - Administration, Boards and Charters (incl. Correspondence) (Box 0023, Folder 12)
- The Executive Administration, 1873-1973: The Chancellor, the Senate, and Standing Committees (Box 0023, Folder 13)
- College General - Students (All Categories) (Box 0023, Folder 14)
- College General - Curriculum (Box 0023, Folder 15)
- College General - Curriculum - Changes - Late 19th Century (Box 0023, Folder 16)
- College General - Curriculum - Degree Requirements (Box 0023, Folder 17)
- College General - Curriculum - Electives (Box 0023, Folder 18)
- College General - Curriculum - Miscellaneous (Box 0023, Folder 19)
- College General - Curriculum - Miscellaneous Bibliography (Box 0023, Folder 20)
- College General - "Spirit of '70" Newsweek (Box 0023, Folder 21)
- College of Arts and Science Calendar of Contents in Archives - RG 48, Dean of Arts and Science (3 boxes) (Box 0023, Folder 22)
- College of Arts and Science - Admin. - Dean Walter L. Fleming (Box 0023, Folder 23)
- College of Arts and Science - Admin. - Deans Shahan and Holladay (Box 0023, Folder 24)
- College of Arts and Science - Admin. - Finance (Box 0023, Folder 25)
- College of Arts and Science - Admin. - Physical Plant - Observatory (Box 0023, Folder 26)
- College of Arts and Science - Changing Status (Box 0023, Folder 27)
- College of Arts and Science - Curriculum - Degree - Copies of Certificates awarded 5/28/1880 (Box 0023, Folder 28)
- College of Arts and Science - Curriculum - Admission and Degree Requirements (Box 0023, Folder 29)
- College of Arts and Science - Curriculum - Curriculum Dispute 1936-1937 (Box 0023, Folder 30)
  including F. C. Rand and J. H. Kirkland correspondence
- College of Arts and Science - Curriculum - Departmental Histories - History Department (Box 0023, Folder 31)
- College of Arts and Science - Curriculum - Department of Education - Weeks Brief (Box 0023, Folder 32)
- College of Arts and Science - Curriculum - to 1970's (Box 0023, Folder 33)
  including 1931 and 1938 Reports of Curriculum Committees
- College of Arts and Science - Curriculum - Merriam Report, 1890; Baskervill, 1891 (Box 0023, Folder 34)
- College of Arts and Science - Curriculum - Degrees - B. S. 1971 (Box 0023, Folder 35)
- College of Arts and Science - Curriculum - 1970 (including Black Studies, Overseas Programs, etc.) (Box 0023, Folder 36)
- College of Arts and Science - Curriculum - Report of the Policy Study Group on Non-Traditional Study Programs (Box 0023, Folder 37)
- College of Arts and Science - Curriculum - Undergraduate Teacher Education Program (Box 0023, Folder 38)
- College of Arts and Science - Curriculum - Library (Box 0023, Folder 39)
- College of Arts and Science - Curriculum - Curriculum Dispute, 1936-1937 (Hood Brief) (Box 0023, Folder 40)
- College of Arts and Science - Curriculum - Departmental Histories - Sociology Department - (Box 0023, Folder 41)
  Wayland and Hayes Draft
- College of Arts and Science - Curriculum - Junior and Senior Colleges (Box 0023, Folder 42)
- College of Arts and Science - Faculty (Box 0023, Folder 43)
- College of Arts and Science - Faculty - Dyer Speech (located in two books -pages are marked) (Box 0023, Folder 44)
- College of Arts and Science - Faculty - Academic Freedom (Box 0023, Folder 45)
- College of Arts and Science - Faculty - Retirements…Benefits (Box 0023, Folder 46)
- College of Arts and Science - Faculty - Awards (Box 0023, Folder 47)
- College of Arts and Science - Faculty - Research (Box 0023, Folder 48)
- College of Arts and Science - Faculty - Overview 1972-1979 (Box 0023, Folder 49)
- College of Arts and Science - Faculty - Student Relations (including Dean's Cabinet) (Box 0023, Folder 50)
- College of Arts and Science - Faculty - History Department (including Dan Robison) (Box 0023, Folder 51)
- College of Arts and Science - Students (including Enrollment and Finance) (Box 0023, Folder 52)
- Engineering School - Administration - Dean Landreth (Box 0023, Folder 53)
- Engineering School - Administration - Deans (Box 0023, Folder 54)
- Engineering School - Administration - Dean Hartman (Box 0023, Folder 55)
- Engineering School - Administration - Acting Dean Rowan (Box 0023, Folder 56)
- Engineering School - Administration - Finance (Box 0023, Folder 57)
- Engineering School - Alumni (Box 0023, Folder 58)
- Engineering School - Changing Status (Box 0023, Folder 59)
- Engineering School - Curriculum - 1880-1881; 1887-1888 (Box 0023, Folder 60)
- Engineering School - Curriculum - Admission and Degree Requirements (Box 0023, Folder 61)
- Engineering School - Curriculum and Curriculum Reorganization (Box 0023, Folder 62)
- Engineering School - Faculty (Box 0023, Folder 63)
- Engineering School - Public Service (Box 0023, Folder 64)
- Engineering School - Students (Box 0023, Folder 65)
- Engineering School - General - Kramer Brief (all categories) (Box 0023, Folder 66)
- Engineering School - General - Curriculum (Box 0023, Folder 67)
- Establishment (Box 0023, Folder 68)
- Establishment - Administration - Letters from Garland, Green, McTyeire, and Vanderbilt (Box 0023, Folder 69)
- Establishment - Administration - Central University (Box 0023, Folder 70)
- Establishment - Administration - Board of Trust (Box 0023, Folder 71)
- Establishment - Administration - Finance (Box 0023, Folder 72)
- Establishment - Administration - Finance - Commodore Vanderbilt's Donations (Box 0023, Folder 73)
- Establishment - Administration - Physical Plant (Box 0023, Folder 74)
- Establishment - Administration - Physical Plant Plans approved by C. Vanderbilt (Box 0023, Folder 75)
- Establishment - Administration - Board of Trust - McTyeire (Box 0023, Folder 76)
- Establishment - Curriculum - Prep. School (Box 0023, Folder 77)
- Establishment - Faculty (Box 0023, Folder 78)
- Establishment - Student - Finance (Box 0023, Folder 79)
- Establishment - Administration - Chancellor Garland's Estimates and Plan (Box 0023, Folder 80)
- Establishment - Central University - Charter and Amended Charter of VU (Box 0023, Folder 81)
- Establishment - Law School Curriculum (Box 0023, Folder 82)
- Establishment - Evolution (Box 0023, Folder 83)
- Establishment - Faculty - Lupton's Trip to Europe (Box 0023, Folder 84)
- Establishment - Miscellaneous - Cornerstone (Box 0023, Folder 85)
- Establishment - Miscellaneous - Celebrations - Commencement 1876 (Box 0023, Folder 86)
- Establishment - Miscellaneous - Dedication (Box 0023, Folder 87)
- Establishment - Miscellaneous - Merriam Report (Box 0023, Folder 88)
- Establishment - Miscellaneous - Nashville 1875 (Box 0023, Folder 89)
- Establishment - Miscellaneous - Purpose (Box 0023, Folder 90)
- Establishment - Miscellaneous - Nashville 1870-1880 (Box 0023, Folder 91)
- Establishment - Miscellaneous - Nashville and Vanderbilt University 1880's (Box 0023, Folder 92)
- Graduate School (Box 0023, Folder 93)
- Graduate School - Administration (Box 0023, Folder 94)
- Graduate School - Administration - McKee Brief (Box 0023, Folder 95)
- Graduate School - Administration - Deans - Beach, Leonard; Campbell, Ernest; Davidson, Phillip (Box 0023, Folder 96)
- Graduate School - Administration - Dean (Box 0023, Folder 97)
- Graduate School - Administration - Deans - Lagemann, Robert (Box 0023, Folder 98)
- Graduate School - Changing Status - Fleming to Kirkland (Box 0023, Folder 99)
- Graduate School - Curriculum - Admission and Degree Requirements (Box 0023, Folder 100)
- Graduate School - Curriculum (Box 0023, Folder 101)
- Graduate School - Curriculum - Degrees (including 1st-2nd Ph.D.) (Box 0023, Folder 102)
- Graduate School - Curriculum - Commissioner of Education's Reports 1886-87; 1887-1888 (Box 0023, Folder 103)
- Graduate School - Curriculum - Departmental Histories - Programs (Box 0023, Folder 104)
- Graduate School - Curriculum - Faculty Council Minutes and Committee Reports (Box 0023, Folder 105)
- Graduate School - Curriculum - Master of Arts in Teaching (MAT) Program (Box 0023, Folder 106)
- Graduate School - Curriculum - Institute of Research and Training in the Social Sciences (including the Mitchell Brief) (Box 0024, Folder 1)
- Graduate School - Curriculum - Institutes - Latin America (Box 0024, Folder 2)
- Graduate School - Curriculum - Institutes - Economic Development (Box 0024, Folder 3)
- Graduate School - Curriculum - Institutes - Reports on Ford Foundation Grand and History of Graduate Program in Economic Development (Box 0024, Folder 4)
- Graduate School - Curriculum - Institutes - Proposals for NDFL Fellowships in Latin American Studies (Box 0024, Folder 5)
- Graduate School - Curriculum - Institutes - Brazilian (Box 0024, Folder 6)
- Graduate School - Curriculum - Ford Ph.D.; MAT; Undergraduate Teacher Education -Mitchell Brief (Box 0024, Folder 7)
- Graduate School - Faculty (Box 0024, Folder 8)
- Graduate School - Faculty Research (Box 0024, Folder 9)
- Graduate School - Miscellaneous (Box 0024, Folder 10)
- Graduate School - Miscellaneous - Almanac (Box 0024, Folder 11)
- Graduate School - Miscellaneous - History (Box 0024, Folder 12)
- Graduate School - Students (including Student Council) (Box 0024, Folder 13)
- Graduate School - Students - Geographic Origins, Sex, Race and Total Enrollment (Box 0024, Folder 14)
- Graduate School - General (Box 0024, Folder 15)
- A Strategic Plan for the Graduate School of Management Vanderbilt University (Box 0024, Folder 16)
- Happy History - Miscellaneous and Undated Material (Box 0024, Folder 17)
- Happy History - Correspondence - Requests and Responses (Box 0024, Folder 18)
- Happy History - To 1899 (Box 0024, Folder 19)
- Happy History - 1890-1899 (Box 0024, Folder 20)
- Happy History - 1900-1909 (Box 0024, Folder 21)
- Happy History - 1910-1919 (Box 0024, Folder 22)
- Happy History - 1920-1929 (Box 0024, Folder 23)
- Happy History - 1930-1949 (Box 0024, Folder 24)
- Happy History - 1950-1969 (Box 0024, Folder 25)
- Happy History - 1970- (Box 0024, Folder 26)
- Happy History - Pictures (Box 0024, Folder 27)
- Happy History - Nursing School Students Tape - "The Flood Story" (1937) (Box 0024, Folder 28)
- Happy History - Personal Reminiscences (Box 0024, Folder 29)
- Happy History - Personal Reminiscences - Frank A. Woods Tape (Box 0024, Folder 31)
- Happy History - Personal Reminiscences - Hermon Dean (Box 0024, Folder 32)
- Happy History - Personal Reminiscences - Vaughn, Miss Stella (Box 0024, Folder 33)
- Happy History - Glen Briefs (Box 0024, Folder 34)
- Happy History - J. G. Baker Tape and Documents - The Ghost of Kirkland Tower (Box 0024, Folder 35)
- Law School - Accreditation (Box 0024, Folder 36)
- Law School - Admission to Tennessee Bar (Box 0024, Folder 37)
- Law School - Administration - Finance (including the Hood Brief) (Box 0024, Folder 38)
- Law School - Reorganizations (1900-1901; 1931-1932; Post World War II) (Box 0024, Folder 39)
- Law School - Administration - Dean John Bell Keeble (Box 0024, Folder 40)
- Law School - Administration - Dean E. C. Arnold (Box 0024, Folder 41)
- Law School - Administration - Dean L. Dale Coffman (Box 0024, Folder 42)
- Law School - Administration - Dean John W. Wade (Box 0024, Folder 43)
- Law School - Administration - Deans - Preliminary Briefs (Box 0024, Folder 44)
- Law School - Administration - Dean Robert L. Knauss (Box 0024, Folder 45)
- Law School - Faculty - Publication (Box 0024, Folder 46)
- Law School - Administration - Physical Plant (including the Hood Brief) (Box 0024, Folder 47)
- Law School - Curriculum (Box 0024, Folder 48)
- Law School - Curriculum - Preliminary Brief (Box 0024, Folder 49)
- Law School - Curriculum - Admission and Degree Requirements (Box 0024, Folder 50)
- Law School - Faculty (Box 0024, Folder 51)
- Law School - Faculty Biography (Box 0024, Folder 52)
- Law School - Faculty (H. A. H. Brief) (Box 0024, Folder 53)
- Law School - Integration (Box 0024, Folder 54)
- Law School - Miscellaneous (Box 0024, Folder 55)
- Law School - Miscellaneous - Chancellor Carmichael 1939 (Box 0024, Folder 56)
- Law School - Miscellaneous - Alumnae (Box 0024, Folder 57)
- Law School - Miscellaneous - Alumni (Box 0024, Folder 58)
  pulled reel to reel for reproduction
- Law School - General - Curriculum (including the Hood Brief) (Box 0024, Folder 59)
- Law School - Public Service (Box 0024, Folder 60)
- Law School - Publications (Box 0024, Folder 61)
- Law School - Students (Box 0024, Folder 62)
- Law School - Students - Hood Brief (Box 0025, Folder 1)
- Law School - Students - Publications (Box 0025, Folder 2)
- Law School - General - Articles by Reed, Alfred Z. (Box 0025, Folder 3)
- Law School - General - American Association of Law Schools (AALS), 1947 (Box 0025, Folder 4)
- Law School - General - Faculty (Box 0025, Folder 5)
- Medical Center - A History of Science and Medicine (Box 0025, Folder 6)
- Medical Center - Children's Hospital (Box 0025, Folder 7)
- Medical Center - Hospital - Administration - Integration (Box 0025, Folder 8)
- Medical Center - Administration - Physical Plant (Box 0025, Folder 9)
- Medical Center - Administration - Vice-Chancellor (Box 0025, Folder 10)
- Medical Center - Affiliations (Box 0025, Folder 11)
- Medical Center - Affiliations - City of Nashville General Hospital (Box 0025, Folder 12)
- Medical Center - Affiliations - Davidson County Tuberculosis Hospital (Box 0025, Folder 13)
- Medical Center - Affiliations - Galloway Hospital (Box 0025, Folder 14)
- Medical Center - Changing Status (Box 0025, Folder 15)
- Medical Center - Public Service and Continuing Education (Box 0025, Folder 16)
- Medical Center - Hospital (Box 0025, Folder 17)
- Medical Center - Hospital - Administration (Box 0025, Folder 18)
- Medical Center - Hospital - Administration - Finance (Box 0025, Folder 19)
- Medical Center - Hospital - Administration - Physical Plant (Box 0025, Folder 20)
- Medical Center - Hospital - Administration - Staff (Box 0025, Folder 21)
- Medical Center - Hospital - Miscellaneous (Box 0025, Folder 22)